http://www.gorving.com/privacy-policy

skip to Main Content
Go RVing uses cookies on gorving.com in accordance with our privacy policy. By using this site, you consent to the use of cookies. We use cookies for the following purposes: To enable certain functions of the service, to provide analytics, to store your preferences, and to enable advertisements delivery, including behavioral advertising.
Got it cookies
BENEFITS
Your Basecamp
For the Family
Furry Friends
All the Amenities
Working from the Road
Versatile Vacations
See All
Kara and Nate's Story The World Is Your Oyster Kara and Nate are YouTube travel vloggers who have visited more than 100 countries. See what made their journey through Maine so special.
Watch The video
A Fit For Any Budget
START YOUR JOURNEY
Buying an RV
Renting an RV
RV Shows & Events
Find Services & Parts
Explore Models & Manufacturers
SIGN UP TO HEAR FROM A DEALER IN YOUR AREA
Send us your email to get helpful tips and useful information from our partners.
Enter your email
Continue
Find the right RV for you
Find a Campground
Close Menu
This is RVing
This Is RVing Overview
BENEFITS
See All
Kara and Nate's Story The World Is Your Oyster Kara and Nate are YouTube travel vloggers who have visited more than 100 countries. See what made their journey through Maine so special.
Watch The video
A Fit For Any Budget
Get Started
Get Started Overview
START YOUR JOURNEY
START YOUR JOURNEY
Buying an RV
Renting an RV
SIGN UP TO HEAR FROM A DEALER IN YOUR AREA
Send us your email to get helpful tips and useful information from our partners.
Enter your email
Continue
Find the right RV for you
Find a Campground
Find a dealer
Find A Campground
Search
Search
Leave this field blank
Close Search
Privacy Policy
Policy statement
Go RVing, Inc. located at 1899 Preston White Drive, Reston, VA 20191 (hereafter “Go RVing”) has prepared this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) to describe its practices regarding the collection, use, storage, transfer and other processing of individually identifiable information about you (“Personal Data”). Go RVing is the controller responsible for the processing of Personal Data described in this Policy.
Throughout this document, this website – www.gorving.com - and all other Go RVing-affiliated websites with links to this policy will be collectively referred to as the “Websites.” Services provided by or enabled via the Websites will be referred to as the “Services.”
This Policy applies to all individuals from which Go RVing collects Personal Data, except for Go RVing employees, who are subject to different employment policies and procedures. Please note that this privacy policy may be changed and/or amended from time to time.
Go RVing is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Go RVing websites to which this website, or any other Go RVing website, may link.
Visitors are not obliged to enter their personal data on the Websites. However, access to certain webpages of the Website can be restricted to those who have entered their Personal Data on the Websites and/or those RV Industry Association members, RVDA members, or National Association of RV Parks & Campgrounds members, who support the Go RVing program (“Go RVing Coalition Members”).
What personal data we collect and how we use it
2.1 Legal basis
The processing of your Personal Data described in this Policy is necessary for one or more of the following: entering into an agreement with Go RVing Coalition Member companies, providing the Services to which Go RVing Coalition Member are entitled, as well as providing certain products and/or Services to those that enter their email address, as well as legitimate business interests. Information may also be collected which has been provided to Go RVing based on the explicit consent of the data subject.
2.2 What personal data we collect and use
The categories and types of Personal Data that Go RVing processes are:
Personal details and contact information: this includes without limitation first name, last name, suffix, e-mail, physical address, telephone number, billing address, company, and buying intentions.
Payment information: this includes without limitation credit card information (encrypted) and other payment information details necessary for payment processing, such as billing and shipping address.
2.3 How we use personal data
Except where restricted by local law, Go RVing uses the Personal Data listed above for the following purposes.
Entering into and continuing Go RVing Coalition Member contractual relationships with new, existing and former Go RVing Coalition Members: Go RVing processes the Personal Data of Go RVing Coalition Member companies’ contact persons for the purpose of processing the Go RVing Coalition Member companies’ sign-up form and the delivery of services;
Communications:  your information may be used by Go RVing, or if you sign up for the leads database, by Go RVing Coalition Members for marketing purposes.
Administrative Management Tasks: Your Personal Data may be used to monitor the use of Go RVing website(s) in order to provide a more personalized and beneficial experience.
How we store personal data and who can access it
Go RVing maintains an automated record of your Personal Data. Additionally, Go RVing maintains Personal Data in various digital formats, namely the leads database for those that register their email or industry only database for those Go RVing Coalition Members that sign-up for access to industry only sections of the website.
The persons and entities that are authorized to have access to your Personal Data are:
All Go RVing staff based in the offices in Reston, VA (1899 Preston White Drive) as well as telecommute employees within the United States; and
external professional service providers, such as IT systems services, including, but not limited to, cloud service providers, online domain/website hosting supplier, database software supplier, payment card processors, and web analysis companies; only to the extent that they have access in the delivery of their IT services and without the ability to process that data other than at the express direction and control of Go RVing.
Where Go RVing engages a third-party processor to process Personal Data on its behalf, such as IT service providers used in the normal course of business, Go RVing will, when applicable, delegate such processing in writing and will choose a processor that provides sufficient guarantees with respect to technical and organizational security measures governing the relevant processing. These third-party processors can be used to provide the Services to you, process payment card information or analyze how you use our Websites.
From time to time, Go RVing may also need to disclose Personal Data to other parties, such as any organization with whom Go RVing co-organizes an event. Go RVing may share Personal Data with these third parties when it is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Go RVing. Such legitimate interests can include coordinating administrative and logistical needs for an event, communicating with the appropriate parties about an event, etc.
Go RVing’s employees or any of Go RVing’s contractual partners who have access to your data in order to provide services to Go RVing are obliged to keep such information in confidence and may not use these data for any other purpose than performing their contractual missions for Go RVing.
Other than as described above, Go RVing does not disclose, sell, rent or share any personal data about you with other entities without prejudice to any statutory obligation to do so by law, official or court orders, except with your previous explicit consent.
Your information is kept in the United States and we do not transfer it outside of the United States.
Security
Go RVing maintains appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect against unauthorized or unlawful processing of Personal Data and/or against accidental loss, alteration, disclosure or access, or accidental or unlawful destruction of or damage to Personal Data. These measures are aimed at ensuring the on-going integrity and confidentiality of Personal Data.
Data retention
Go RVing will retain your Personal Data only for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes we have collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.
To determine the appropriate retention period for Personal Data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the Personal Data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your Personal Data, the purposes for which we process your Personal Data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal information so that it can no longer be associated with you, in which case we may use such information without further notice to you.
Your rights
You have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your Personal Data at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.
To the extent required by applicable law, you have the right to: (i) have access to your Personal Data; (ii) the right to have inaccurate data corrected or removed, (iii) the right to object to the processing of your Personal Data; (iv) the right to restrict Go RVing’s use of your Personal Data; (v) the right to receive your Personal Data in a usable electronic format and transmit it to a third party (right to “data portability”); and (vi) the right to lodge a complaint with the duly authorized and relevant local data protection authority.
In particular, Go RVing is committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any complaint or concerns about privacy. If, however, you believe that Go RVing has not been able to assist with your complaint or concern, you have the right to make a complaint with the competent authority of the European Union Member State where you reside or work or where you believe that your rights have been infringed.
In these cases, or if you have any other questions or wishes in connection with your personal data, please contact Go RVing by sending a letter/fax/e-mail or calling at:
Go RVing
1899 Preston White Drive
Reston, Virginia 20191
United States
Tel: +1(703) 620-6003
Email: gorving@rvia.org
Policy updates
In case of any material changes to the way in which Go RVing collects or uses Personal Data, the type of Personal Data it collects or any other aspect of this Policy, Go RVing will issue a revised Policy.
Cookie Policy
This Policy applies to websites owned and operated by Go RVing, including, but not limited to, www.gorving.com. Throughout this document, this website and all other Go RVing affiliated websites with links to this policy will be collectively referred to as the “Websites.” Services provided by or enabled via the Websites will be referred to as the “Services.”
The Websites are maintained to enable Go RVing Coalition Members, public visitors, and registered users to access information that educates and informs potential RVers about the benefits and accessibility of RVing and that assists RV dealers in its promotional efforts.
This Policy applies to all coalition members, visitors and registered users entering this site (“you”), regardless of the physical location of the individual accessing user. By entering this site, you are expressly accepting the conditions outlined below. Please note that this privacy policy may be changed and/or amended from time to time and that by re-entering this site you will accept those changed or amended clauses of the privacy policy at the time of re-entry.
Go RVing is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Go RVing websites to which this website, or any other Go RVing website, may link.
IP addresses and Cookies
IP addresses
When visiting the Websites, Go RVing Coalition Members’, visitors’ and registered users’ (collectively, “Users”) IP addresses are automatically collected by Go RVing for system administration and statistical purposes in order to optimize the user experience of the Websites.
Depending on the circumstances, collected IP address data may allow conclusions to be drawn about Users’ interaction with the Websites. However, Go RVing does not combine IP addresses with other information on the Users and cannot relate IP addresses with the identity of the User. Go RVing solely use IP addresses as such and is not able to identify specific Users by way of IP addresses.
Your IP address is logged when visiting our Websites, but our analytic software only uses this information to track how many unique visitors we have.
“Cookies”
Cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain websites. Provided that you have accepted the use of cookies, Go RVing may use first-party “cookies” to provide certain functions of the service, to provide Go RVing with website usage analytics, to store your preferences, and to enable advertisements delivery, including behavioral advertising. The cookies that Go RVing uses are session/temporary cookies with short-term future expiration dates.
As part of Google Analytics, Go RVing also uses first-party cookies to monitor traffic to Websites. The purpose of these cookies is to understand – at an anonymous, statistical level – who our Websites’ visitors are, what brings them to the Websites and what use they make of it. The longest cookie lifespan of these cookies is 2 years.
In addition, you can learn more about controlling the cookies that may be placed in the following web browsers or applications by reviewing such browsers or applications policies: Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer, Edge and Safari.
Go RVing also uses third-party cookies. Just like with first-party cookies, these cookies are used to provide certain functions of the service, to provide Go RVing with website usage analytics, to store your preferences, and to enable advertisements delivery, including behavioral advertising.
Want to learn more?
Send us your email to get helpful tips and useful information from our partners.
Enter your email
Continue
* Indicates the field is required.
Your Name
*
Email
*
Zip Code
ZIP/Postal Code
*
I'm likely to buy/rent within...
3 months
6 months
1 year
> 1 year
Are you currently and RV owner?
Yes
No
Previously
I'm interested in...
Buying
Renting
By submitting this form I consent to providing my information to Go RVing and understand that I may be contacted by Go RVing and/or Go RVing’s partners.
*
Leave this field blank
